reppify.com 2019-08-27

# Privacy Policy | Reppify

Reppify provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of the information that we collect and receive from users of our services at [www.reppify.com](http://www.reppify.com/) (the _"Services"_ ). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to use through the Services. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service (the _"Terms"_ ). This Privacy Policy applies to information that you provide to us through the Services.

As used in this policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

## Information Collection and Use

When using our Services, we will ask you for certain personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and information on your use or potential use of the Services and related services ("Personal Information"). Personal Information that we might collect would include things like, your name, phone number, your email address and home and business postal addresses, credit card or other billing information, and website URLs, and any other information or data that you provide to the Services, such as any of your social networking site accounts that you link to your Account. You are under no obligation to provide us with these credentials, and can de-link your accounts at any time. We use your Personal Information to provide the Services and administer your inquiries. You may change or delete any information that you provide; please use caution when linking or posting any Personal Information, as such information may be viewed by other users of the Services.

We use Personal Information for the following purposes: (i) to administer the Services, (ii) to enable users to easily navigate the Services, (iii) to provide, improve and optimize the Services, (iv) to better understand users needs and interests, (iv) to personalize your experience, (v) to provide you with software updates and/or product announcements, and (vi) to provide you with further information and offers from us that we believe you may find useful or interesting. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or select the appropriate option in your user profile. (See "Changing or Deleting Information," below.)

When you visit the Services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Services, pages of our website and Services that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Services, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Services and for the Services' technical administration, to increase our Services' functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors' needs. For example, some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Services again, it will recognize you and serve information appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Services meet the criteria required to process their requests.

We also use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Services. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services and to monitor aggregate usage by users of the Services and web traffic routing on the Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Services and then close your browser. Third party advertisers on the Services may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions or all functionality of the Services.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide the Services, when we otherwise have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

_Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information._ We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose non-identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic and analytical profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

_Service Providers._ We may employ third party companies and individuals to process your payments, facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Services-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Services' features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Services are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other trusted entities for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications by setting the appropriate option in your user profile or by contacting us at [support [at] reppify.com](https://web.archive.org/web/20190827230940id_/http://reppify.com/privacy-policy/support%20\[at\]%20reppify.com).

_Reppify Clients._ We will share your Personal Information with Reppify clients requesting your Reppify Score only with your permission. If you have provided your Personal Information to the Services to enable Reppify to generate a Reppify Score for use by employers for employment screening purposes or other uses regulated by the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA), Reppify will not create a Reppify Score about you for a Reppify client requesting your Reppify Score unless Reppify's client completes a certification required by the FCRA. In this certification, Reppify's client certifies to Reppify that the information obtained through the Services is sought to be used for (or to be provided for) employment purposes; tenant screening purposes; purposes related to a business transaction initiated by the consumer; other permissible purposes as defined by the FCRA); and no other purpose, and that it has, to the extent required by applicable law, obtained your informed consent to use such information, including, when applicable, your Personal Information.

_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement._ Reppify cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Reppify or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

_Business Transfers._ We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information

All registered users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile by contacting us at [support [at] reppify.com](https://web.archive.org/web/20190827230940id_/http://reppify.com/privacy-policy/support%20\[at\]%20reppify.com) or by making the appropriate modifications in your user account preferences. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you deactivate your account as described in the Terms, we will lock down your Personal Information and will not share or sell it with other Reppify clients or third party providers; however, we may still incorporate non-identifying information into analytics provided for Reppify clients. If you would like us to remove your records from our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation to retain the record.

## Security

We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access and disclosure including encrypting your communication by utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Services in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

## International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Reppify may transfer your Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## EU and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield

Reppify complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. Reppify has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Reppify commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact Reppify at: [support@reppify.com.](mailto:support@reppify.com) You may also contact us to have your information removed from our systems at the same address.

Reppify has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact or visit JAMS at <https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield> for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you. 

Reppify commits to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) and comply with the advice given by such authorities with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU and Switzerland in the context of the employment relationship.

o Reppify is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC)  
o Under certain conditions, individuals may be able to invoke binding arbitration  
o Reppify's liability in cases of onward transfers to third parties are covered here: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=3-ACCOUNTABILITY-FOR-ONWARD-TRANSFER>  
o The [Recourse, Enforcement and Liability Principle](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=7-RECOURSE-ENFORCEMENT-AND-LIABILITY) provides that “In the context of an onward transfer, a Privacy Shield organization has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. The Privacy Shield organization shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless the organization proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.”   

## Links to Other Sites

Our Services may contain links to other websites for news and other information. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's websites. The fact that we may link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. Our Privacy Policy only applies to the Services and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. You should check the privacy policies of those sites before providing your personal information to them.

## Children's Information

The Services are not directed to children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, please contact us. If we become aware that a member is under the age of 13 and has provided us with Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will delete such information from our files.

## Agreement and Changes

By using the Services, you agree to the current Privacy Policy and Terms, to which this Privacy Policy is incorporated. Reppify reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, discontinue, or terminate the Services or to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on the Services or providing you with notice of the modification. We will also indicate when such terms are effective below. By continuing to access or use the Services after we have posted a modification or have provided you with notice of a modification, you are indicating that you agree to be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If the modified Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to cease using the Services.

## Contacing Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support [at] reppify.com](https://web.archive.org/web/20190827230940id_/http://reppify.com/privacy-policy/support%20\[at\]%20reppify.com).

**Last Updated:** April 25th, 2018
